americanpressinstitute.org 2003-04-01

# Privacy Policy

|  |  **Privacy Policy**

The American Press Institute has a long tradition of honoring the privacy of its users. 

The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. 

####  Information Automatically Logged 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to gather statistical data about usage of our Web site and to administer our Web site. 

####  Cookies 

Our site uses cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes. 

####  Registration Forms 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, e-mail, and postal address), financial information (like their bank account or credit card numbers), unique identifiers (like their social security number), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). 

Contact information from the registration forms is used to ship information about our company. User contact information is also used to get in touch with users when necessary, and for other purposes. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. 

Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity. 

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.   
We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

####  Order Forms and Event Registration 

Our site uses order forms to request information about products and services and to register for seminars and other events. We collect contact information (like e-mail address), financial information (like account or credit card numbers), unique identifiers (like a social security number), and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level). 

Contact information from the order forms is used to ship purchases, invoices and information about our company and events. Contact information is also used to get in touch with visitors when necessary, and for other purposes. For instance, when you register for a seminar or event, contact information is shared with other seminar participants and with discussion leaders and speakers. 

When you register for a seminar or event on our site, you have granted us permission to release the information you entered. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Financial information that is collected is used to bill users for products and services. 

Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity. 

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.   
We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

####  Surveys 

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like e-mail address), financial information (like account or credit card numbers), unique identifiers (like social security number), and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level). 

Contact information from the surveys is used to ship information about our company. Contact information is also used to get in touch with the user when necessary, and for other purposes. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity. 

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.   
We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

####  External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. **American Press Institute** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

####  Public Forums 

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, Web and e-mail discussions and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

We require user registrations to encourage responsible and respectful use of our discussion systems. 

We do not sell or share site registration information with outside firms or individuals. 

If you create a user profile, it will be available to other registered users. 

Your e-mail address will be available to other registered users. 

API may occasionally send users news and information about API. 

####  Security 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. 

####  Supplementation of Information 

This site supplements the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties. This practice is primarily used to update user profiles for changes employers and geographic location. 

####  Data Quality/Access 

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

  1. You can send e-mail to [ admin@americanpressinstitute.org ](mailto:admin@americanpressinstitute.org)
  2. You can visit the following URL:  Contact Us 
  3. You can send mail to the following postal address:  11690 Sunrise Valley Drive  
Reston, VA 20191 
  4. You can call the following telephone number: (703) 620-3611 

##  Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:   

|  | 
|  |  **Privacy Policy**

The American Press Institute has a long tradition of honoring the privacy of its users. 

The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site. 

####  Information Automatically Logged 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to gather statistical data about usage of our Web site and to administer our Web site. 

####  Cookies 

Our site uses cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes. 

####  Registration Forms 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name, e-mail, and postal address), financial information (like their bank account or credit card numbers), unique identifiers (like their social security number), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level). 

Contact information from the registration forms is used to ship information about our company. User contact information is also used to get in touch with users when necessary, and for other purposes. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services. 

Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity. 

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.   
We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

####  Order Forms and Event Registration 

Our site uses order forms to request information about products and services and to register for seminars and other events. We collect contact information (like e-mail address), financial information (like account or credit card numbers), unique identifiers (like a social security number), and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level). 

Contact information from the order forms is used to ship purchases, invoices and information about our company and events. Contact information is also used to get in touch with visitors when necessary, and for other purposes. For instance, when you register for a seminar or event, contact information is shared with other seminar participants and with discussion leaders and speakers. 

When you register for a seminar or event on our site, you have granted us permission to release the information you entered. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Financial information that is collected is used to bill users for products and services. 

Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity. 

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.   
We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

####  Surveys 

Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like e-mail address), financial information (like account or credit card numbers), unique identifiers (like social security number), and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level). 

Contact information from the surveys is used to ship information about our company. Contact information is also used to get in touch with the user when necessary, and for other purposes. 

Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity. 

Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.   
We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences. 

####  External Links 

This site contains links to other sites. **American Press Institute** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

####  Public Forums 

This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, Web and e-mail discussions and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

We require user registrations to encourage responsible and respectful use of our discussion systems. 

We do not sell or share site registration information with outside firms or individuals. 

If you create a user profile, it will be available to other registered users. 

Your e-mail address will be available to other registered users. 

API may occasionally send users news and information about API. 

####  Security 

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. 

####  Supplementation of Information 

This site supplements the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties. This practice is primarily used to update user profiles for changes employers and geographic location. 

####  Data Quality/Access 

This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided: 

  1. You can send e-mail to [ admin@americanpressinstitute.org ](mailto:admin@americanpressinstitute.org)
  2. You can visit the following URL:  Contact Us 
  3. You can send mail to the following postal address:  11690 Sunrise Valley Drive  
Reston, VA 20191 
  4. You can call the following telephone number: (703) 620-3611 

##  Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:   

|  |
